And now you're done with lesson two. Woohoo. You've made
a huge step in being able to transfer data from
a server and bring it all the way down to
your device. Think about all the possibilities now of valuable information
you could bring down to users to be available at
their fingertips. And that's pretty powerful. Speaking about making an impact,
have you thought about what you're going to do for your
final project yet? You can choose any topic that you want.
Share your ideas in the class discussion forum, and
you can share with your friends on social media too.
Over to beta now, while I take a quick nap
on this Done pillow. I'll see you in lesson three.